Hello everyone! I've got something really exciting to show you. I received new
shoes from Giaro and I'm going to try them on now. I already own these shoes and
thanks to Giaro who sent me another three pairs so I can show you different
colors and different styles. Let's start right away. I'll start with the black
ones because I love black. It's super easy to dress because they have a zipper.
I think they already look great and make a nice shape of the leg. Oh and one little
design feature I totally adore is that the lacing is not normal
Yeah, cotton lacing but elastics.
I love how they look and I think they do look more uncomfortable than they are.
If that makes sense. Due to this high angle here you may have the impression that it is hard to stand or to walk in but it's not really. It's rather pretty okay. So I can walk in them, I can stand in them. It's not like my feet are instantly hurting. So it's totally fine. It's rather more comfortable than they look.
My favorite thing about these is that they shine.
They're so shiny. I think they upgrade every cool leggings even more.
And I'm glad I combined it with the colorful leggings because it even emphasized them more.
I've already worn them for a few video and photo shoots but I did not wear these yet.
And they're pink, so let's try these next
I changed into a dress because I thought it's going to be a better fit for the shoes.
And I can already tell that these look amazing.
I mean the color is wow.
Super bright and it really makes a nice foot I think.
So when I look in the mirror, it's great sitting legs and feet, so to say.
This is a great look. I love it.
I can totally recommend them for slim feet, because they're not too wide.
Also the straps are not too wide, which is a problem I have a lot.
But not with these ones, so I'm a happy girl.
So here's the proof. I can walk on them and a lot of people always ask, oh how do you manage to do that?
And I have to say it's really practice. You have to practice walking in such shoes.
So start small and then use the higher ones.
I still love this color. I wouldn't have thought so. It's totally pink which is not my color but for these shoes it's great.
and on to the next color then silver I think these are going to look really really cool
this is the statement outfit for the statement shoes i thought let's do a bit of a high fashion
outfit because these shoes are just so cool with their silver and i really love how it looks
Yeah, that was a great choice. I'm happy about this. And I'm also thinking that these shoes are really cool.
I know I say cool a lot of times, but for these, cool is like the perfect term. Or whatever. Extravagant.
I actually bought this jumpsuit for a photo shooting and I thought I'll do accessories
golden with the golden shoes but then I received these and I was like no I think I'm going
to switch to silver and yeah there's some high fashion pics planned in the harbor or
To be honest at the beginning I was a bit afraid because the heel is very very thin and I thought oh this is going to be wobbly and yeah I'm not going to feel comfortable with them but I have to tell you this is like rock solid.
I'm not wonky or whatever so yeah no problems I feel totally safe and I did
not experience that with a lot of shoes so far with these small heels here and
also I did not lose any rivets until now because I'm going to change into these
I changed into this last pair I already owned them so I know that I like them
because they also look really nice and elegant and they make this outfit a bit
more wearable for daily wear. I wouldn't wear this in my daily life but maybe to a
wedding or macho party or whatever I don't know. So yeah I don't know which
shoes I prefer for the jumpsuit though. Depends on the occasion. Yeah I don't know.
which one was your favorite pair? Would you like to tell me in the comments? Then
leave a comment below and also have a look at the description text because
I'll link every pair and yeah I'll tell you everything again in the description
text. By the way I'm wearing size 40 and they fit pretty good so nothing to
complain here. Okay I had a lot of fun showing you these shoes. I'm going to use
them I'm really sure for a lot of pictures and yeah maybe for going out so
I wish you a nice day hope you had a nice time here see you in the next video
bye